

Hassan Abdul Hadi Muthana

Mobile: +964-7712000032

E-mail: hassanabdhadi@yahoo.com

CAREER OBJECTIVE

To seek new challenges in Finance and Accounts and to be part of a reputed organizations that offers potential growth, advancement opportunities and stability, wherein I can utilize my experience to wards achieving company objectives and personal growth where my background and experience can be utilized and further enhanced.

PERSONAL DATA

• **Date of Birth** : February 11, 1978

Nationality : IraqiMarital Status : Married

WORK EXPERIENCE

Nabors Drilling International—Iraq —Erbil. May, 2014 — Present.

Title: Senior Accountant.

The Nabors companies own and operate approximately 501 land drilling and approximately 743 land workover and well-servicing rigs in North America. Nabors' actively marketed offshore fleet consists of 40 platform rigs, 12 jack-up units and 4 barge rigs in the United States and multiple international markets. In addition, Nabors manufactures top drives and drilling instrumentation systems and provides comprehensive oilfield hauling, engineering, civil construction, logistics and facilities maintenance, and project management services. Nabors participates in most of the significant oil, gas and geothermal markets in the world, We have in Kurdistan Drilling Oil & Gas work in Rovia & Sarta, my work as Senior Accountant between Erbil and Basra Office.

- Working on oracle system "ERP version 12"
- Working on NSG system"
- Managing Bank Accounts.
- Issued, controlled & reimbursed petty cash for the staff.
- Passed Journal Vouchers & Payments for different Vendors, Sub Contractors & Suppliers
- Prepare Social Security Calculation for our employees to pay it to Kurdistan Government Sector.
- Rigs Visiting In Rovia & Sarta,.

Nabors Drilling International—Iraq —Basra.

Sep, 2011 – Apr, 2014. Title: Senior Accountant.

The Nabors companies own and operate approximately 501 land drilling and approximately 743 land workover and well-servicing rigs in North America. Nabors' actively marketed offshore fleet consists of 40 platform rigs, 12 jack-up units and 4 barge rigs in the United States and multiple international markets. In addition, Nabors manufactures top drives and drilling instrumentation systems and provides comprehensive oilfield hauling, engineering, civil construction, logistics and facilities maintenance, and project management services. Nabors participates in most of the significant oil, gas and geothermal markets in the world, We have in Iraq Drilling Oil & Gas work in North Romaila & Majnoon, my work as Senior Accountant between Dubai Office and Iraq Office.

- Working on oracle system "ERP version 12"
- Working on NSG system"
- Managing Bank Accounts.
- Issued, controlled & reimbursed petty cash for the staff.
- Passed Journal Vouchers & Payments for different Vendors, Sub Contractors & Suppliers
- Prepare Social Security Calculation for our employees to pay it to Iraqi Government Sector.
- Prepare Income Tax Calculation for our employees to pay it to Iraqi Government Sector.
- Contact persons between Nabors Company and Different Government Sector In Basra & Baghdad
- Rigs Visiting In North of Romaila And Majnoon.

 $Nabors\ Drilling\ International-\ UAE-Dubai.$

July, 2011 – Auget, 2011. Title: Senior Accountant.

itle: Senior Accountant.

The Nabors companies own and operate approximately 501 land drilling and approximately 743 land workover and well-servicing rigs in North America. Nabors' actively marketed offshore fleet consists of 40 platform rigs, 12 jack-up units and 4 barge rigs in the United States and multiple international markets. In addition, Nabors manufactures top drives and drilling instrumentation systems and provides comprehensive oilfield hauling, engineering, civil construction, logistics and facilities maintenance, and project management services. Nabors participates in most of the significant oil, gas and geothermal markets in the world, The Head Office in Middle East in Dubai.

- Working on oracle system "ERP version 12"
- Working on NSG system"
- Managing Bank Accounts.
- Issued, controlled & reimbursed petty cash for the staff.
- Passed Journal Vouchers & Payments for different Vendors, Sub Contractors & Suppliers

EMIRATES UTILITIES COMPANY HOLDING - UAE - Abu Dhabi.

A Subsidiary Company of AL Qudra Holding.

Jan, 2008 – June, 2011. Title: Accountant.

EUCH is limited liability Company that is jointly established by AL Qudra Holding of Abu Dhabi and Mohammed Abdul Mohsin AL Kharafi of Kuwait. Through a series of subsidiary companies (Special Purpose Vehicles – SPV) EUCH is managing and executing privately financed infrastructure investment projects using the BOOT and BOO strategies.

- Ensuring that all financial data produced is accurate & dependable.
- Migration All Data from Old System "ATS" to New Systems "ERP version 12"
- Working on oracle system "ERP version 12"
- Providing monthly financial statements and compile reports, confirming the accuracy of the same
- Managing the financial accounting & cost accounting functions.
- Managing Bank Accounts.
- Co-ordinating and interacting with external Audit and Law enforcement agencies.

KHARAFI NATIONAL – Iraq September, 2003 – Jan 2008.

Title: Accountant.

A recent branch for KHARAFI NATIONAL – Kuwait established in Iraq executing major projects from KBR, Washington Group,

- Handled & Controlled Current Accounts between various areas.
- Passed Journal Vouchers & Payments for different Vendors, Sub Contractors & Suppliers
- Accountants, Payroll Assistants & Data Processing Operator.
- Weekly reporting to Kuwait Head Office for overall financial aspects.
- Prepared periodic Cash forecasts as per the expected costs.
- Audited the whole Payments, Journal Vouchers, Salaries & reports before entering to GL.
- Arrange periodic accounts analysis to ensure accuracy of monthly trial balance.
- Preparing the Monthly, Quarterly, Semi Annually and Annually Financial Statements.
- Prepare outstanding cost for preparation of monthly cost report.
- Handled & controlled Prepaid Expenses.
- Analyzed accounts to make sure that all transaction are recorded accurately.
- Handled Sub Contractors payments as per the stipulated conditions
- Processed accounting vouchers & journal entries.
- Handled Creditors payments.
- Handled Letter of Guarantees, following up bank charges rates for issuing guarantees & controlling bank facilities.
- Verified necessary approvals are obtained before payment or cost loading
- Handled & Controlling General & Different business Expenses as per the levels of authority
- Calculated Business trips for the company staff.
- Issued, controlled & reimbursed petty cash for the staff.

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

BASRA UNIVERSITY, Basra, Iraq.

 Major Accounting Graduation Year 2002

COMPUTER SKILLS

- Proficient in MS. Excel.
- Proficient in MS. Word.
- Proficient acquiring data & information using internet and search engines.

LANGUAGES

• English: Excellent Reading writing & conversation.

COURSES

International Accounting Standards: KPMG.
IFRIC 12 – Service Concession Arrangement: KPMG.

PERSONALITY

- Self motivated, work well under pressure
- Hard working, Ambitious.
- Willing to travel and relocate to enhance my career & improve my experience.

References

- Mr. Nourallah Khan-Director Nabors Drilling Mobile +971501005657
- Ms. Roslinah Riteby Finance Manager Nabors Drilling Mobile +971561760430
- Mr. Prakash Nouronnah-Finance Supervisor Nabors Drilling Mobile +919167402091
- Mr. Salman Yusuf-Finance Supervisor Nabors Drilling Mobile +971528490442
- Mr. Mohamed Aboush-Director Kharafinational Mobile +96597246082
- Mr. Ayman Abou Ouf-Finance Manager Kharafinational-Kuwait Mobile +96599434078
- Mr. Mohammed Orabi-Finance Manager Kharafinational-UAE Mobile +971504560980

REFERENCES FURNISHED UPON REQUEST.